Contact

silverspring.ed@sunriseseni orliving.com

www.linkedin.com/in/susan-maupin-13b48b55 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing Management Nursing Care Nursing Education

Certifications

Assisted Living Manager (ALM)
First Aid/CPR Instructor

Susan Maupin

Executive Director/Registered Nurse at Sunrise Senior Living Pasadena, Maryland

Summary

Experienced Executive Director with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Nursing Management, Clinical Research, CPR Instruction, Customer Service, and Nursing Education. Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Registered Nursing, Nursing Administration, Nursing Research and Clinical Nursing from College of Notre Dame of Maryland.

Experience

Sunrise Senior Living
Executive Director/Registered Nurse
April 2006 - Present (14 years 4 months)
Sunrise of Silver Spring, MD

Amedysis Home Care Clinical Supervisor August 2004 - April 2006 (1 year 9 months)

North Arundel Hospital Home Care Clinical Supervisor October 1994 - August 2004 (9 years 11 months)

Education

College of Notre Dame of Maryland
Bachelor's degree, Registered Nursing, Nursing Administration, Nursing
Research and Clinical Nursing · (2004 - 2006)

Indian River Community College
Associate's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (1991 - 1994)